Guide to the David Wojnarowicz Papers MSS.092
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series XII: Library, 1892-1994
  - Marko, Ksynia. Embroidery. London: Octopus, 1982., cuid27566 (Box XII.22, Folder 446)
  - Marks, C. W.; Ed. Collection de Potpourris des Meilleurs Operas. Hambourg: Aug. Cranz, [n. d. ]. [source material], undated; cuid27567 (Box XII.22, Folder 447)
  - Marshall, John. Rail: Guinness Factbook. London: Guinness Books, 1985., cuid27568 (Box XII.22, Folder 448)
  - Martin, Rupert, ed. The View from Above: 125 Years of Aerial Photography. London: The Photographers' Gallery, 1983., cuid27569 (Box XII.22, Folder 449)
  - Mathers, Michael. Riding the Rails. Boston: Houghton Mifflin, 1974., cuid27570 (Box XII.22, Folder 450)
  - Matthiessen, Peter. The Cloud Forest. New York: Penguin, 1987., cuid27571 (Box XII.22, Folder 451)
  - ---. The Snow Leopard. New York: Penguin, 1987., cuid27572 (Box XII.22, Folder 452)
  - The Mayas. Mexico: GV Editores, 1985., cuid27573 (Box XII.22, Folder 453)
  - McCarthy, Cormac. Blood Meridian. New York: Ecco Press, 1988., cuid27574 (Box XII.22, Folder 454)
  - McCormick, Ken and Hamilton Darby Perry. Images of War. New York: Orion Books, 1990./ McGuire, Thomas, DDS. The Tooth Trip: An Oral Experience. New York: Random House, 1972., cuid27575 (Box XII.22, Folder 455)
  - McKibben, Bill. The End of Nature. New York: Random House, 1989., cuid27576 (Box XII.22, Folder 456)
  - McMillan, Terry. Disappearing Acts. New York: Washington Square Press, 1990., cuid27577 (Box XII.23, Folder 457)
  - Medical Infrared Photography. New York: Eastman Kodak, 1973., cuid27578 (Box XII.23, Folder 458)
  - The Medici Aesop. Trans. Bernard McTigue. New York: Harry N. Abrams, 1989., cuid27579 (Box XII.23, Folder 459)
  - Meinkoth, Norman A. The Audubon Society Field Guide to North American Seashore Creatures. New York: Alfred A. Knopf, 1981., cuid27580 (Box XII.23, Folder 460)
  - Meiselas, Susan. Nicaragua. New York: Pantheon Books, 1981., cuid27581 (Box XII.23, Folder 461)
  - Meletzis, Spyros, and Helen Papdakis. Archaologisches Nationalmusem Athen. Munchen: Verlag Schnell & Steiner, 1977., cuid27582 (Box XII.23, Folder 462)
  - Menen, Aubrey. Cities in the Sand. New York: The Dial Press, 1973., cuid27583 (Box XII.23, Folder 463)
  - Meyer, Franz Sales. Handbook of Ornament. New York: Dover Publications, 1957., cuid27584 (Box XII.23, Folder 464)
  - Meyer, Karl E. Teotihuacan. New York: Newsweek, 1973., cuid27585 (Box XII.23, Folder 465)
  - Michals, Duane. Homage to Cavafy. Danbury, NH: Addison House, 1978., cuid27586 (Box XII.23, Folder 466)
  - Michaux, Henri. Selected Writings. Trans. Richard Ellman. New York: New Directions, 1968., cuid27587 (Box XII.23, Folder 467)
  - Miller, John and David Pelham. The Facts of Life. New York: Viking, 1984., cuid27588 (Box XII.23, Folder 468)
  - Milne, Lorus and Margery. The Audubon Society Field Guide to North American Insects and Spiders. New York: Alfred A. Knopf, 1988., cuid27589 (Box XII.23, Folder 469)
  - Mishima, Yukio. Confessions of a Mask. New York: New Directions, 1958., cuid27590 (Box XII.23, Folder 470)
  - ---. The Sea of Fertility: Spring Snow. Trans. Michael Gallagher. Vol. 1 New York: Alfred A. Knopf, 1973., cuid27591 (Box XII.23, Folder 471)
  - ---. The Sea of Fertility: Runaway Horses. Trans. Michael Gallagher. Vol. 2 New York: Alfred A. Knopf, 1973., cuid27592 (Box XII.24, Folder 472)
  - ---. The Sea of Fertility: The Temple of Dawn. Trans. Michael Gallagher. Vol. 3 New York: Alfred A. Knopf, 1973., cuid27593 (Box XII.24, Folder 473)
  - ---. The Sea of Fertility: The Decay of the Angel. Trans. Michael Gallagher. Vol. 4 New York: Alfred A. Knopf, 1973., cuid27594 (Box XII.24, Folder 474)
  - Mitchner, Stuart. Indian Action: An American Journey to the Great Fair of the East. Boston: Little, Brown and Company, 1976., cuid27595 (Box XII.24, Folder 475)
  - Moir, Alfred. Caravaggio. New York: Harry N. Abrams, 1989., cuid27596 (Box XII.24, Folder 476)
  - Momento Mori. [n. p. ]: Centro Cultural/Arte Contemporaneo, 1986., cuid27597 (Box XII.24, Folder 477)
  - Monette, Paul. Becoming a Man. New York: HBJ, 1992., cuid27598 (Box XII.24, Folder 478)
  - Moon, Dolly M. My Very First Book of Cowboy Songs. New York: Dover, 1982., cuid27599 (Box XII.24, Folder 479)
  - Moore, Keith L. The Developing Human. Philadelphia: W. B Saunders Co., 1977., cuid27600 (Box XII.24, Folder 480)
  - Morales, Demetrio Sodi. The Maya World. Mexico: Minutiae Mexicana, 1976., cuid27601 (Box XII.24, Folder 481)
  - Morris, Jan. Journeys. New York: Oxford University Press, 1984., cuid27602 (Box XII.24, Folder 482)
  - Mortuary Posts of the Giryama. New York: Friends of Bronx Community Art Gallery, April 28-May 20, 1978., cuid27603 (Box XII.24, Folder 483)
  - Motor Auto Repair Manual. Second Vintage Car Edition, 1953-61. New York: Motor, 1981., cuid27604 (Box XII.24, Folder 484)
  - Mrabet, Mohammed. Marriage with Papers. Trans. Paul Bowles. Bolinas, CA: Tombouctou Books, 1986., cuid27605 (Box XII.24, Folder 485)
  - Mueller, Cookie. Walking Through Clear Water in a Pool Painted Black. New York: Semiotext(e), 1990., cuid27606 (Box XII.24, Folder 486)
  - Muench, David, and Donald D. Pike. Anasazi: Ancient People of the Rock. Palo Alto, CA: America West Publishing Co., 1974., cuid27607 (Box XII.25, Folder 487)
  - Muktananda, Swami. Does Death Really Exist? South Fallsburg, NY: SYDA Foundation, 1981., cuid27608 (Box XII.25, Folder 488)
  - ---. I Have Become Alive. South Fallsburg, NY: SYDA Foundation, 1985., cuid27609 (Box XII.25, Folder 489)
  - ---. Kundalini: The Secret of Life. South Fallsburg, NY: SYDA Foundation, 1979., cuid27610 (Box XII.25, Folder 490)
  - ---. Meditate. Albany: State University of New York Press, 1980., cuid27611 (Box XII.25, Folder 491)
  - Municipal Index and Atlas. New York: American City Magazine Corporation, 1940., cuid27612 (Box XII.25, Folder 492)
  - ---. New York: American City Magazine Corporation,1941., cuid27613 (Box XII.25, Folder 493)
  - The Nation. 13 Feb. 1989, cuid27614 (Box XII.25, Folder 494)
  - ---. 20 Mar. 1989, cuid27615 (Box XII.25, Folder 495)
  - The National Enquirer. 31 July 1990., cuid27616 (Box XII.25, Folder 496)
  - National Geographic [cover altered]. Vol. 154, No. 4 October 1978., cuid27617 (Box XII.25, Folder 497)
  - National and International Studio Programs 1983-1984: P. S. 1, The Clocktower. New York: Institute for Art and Urban Resources, 1984., cuid27618 (Box XII.25, Folder 499)
  - National Museum of Anthropology, Mexico. Mexico: GV Editores, 1986., cuid27619 (Box XII.25, Folder 500)
  - Neese, Robert. Prison Exposures. Philadelphia: Chilton Company Book Division, 1959., cuid27620 (Box XII.25, Folder 501)
  - Neo York: Report on a Phenomenon. Santa Barbara, CA: University Art Museum, 1984., cuid27621 (Box XII.25, Folder 502)
  - Neruda, Pablo. A New Decade Poems 1958-1967. Trans. Ben Belitt and Alastair Reid. New York: Grove, 1969., cuid27622 (Box XII.25, Folder 503)
  - ---. New Poems. Trans. and Ed. Ben Belitt. New York: Grove, 1972. [Pages 6 and 22 marked], cuid27623 (Box XII.25, Folder 504)
  - New Art Examiner. Nov. 1990, cuid27624 (Box XII.25, Folder 505)
  - New Narrative Painting: Selections from the Metropolitan Museum of Art, New York. Fort Lauderdale, FL: Museum of Art, 1984., cuid27625 (Box XII.25, Folder 506)
  - The New Press Catalogue. New York: W. W. Norton & Co., 1992., cuid27626 (Box XII.25, Folder 507)
  - Newsweek. 11 Mar 1985., cuid27627 (Box XII.25, Folder 508)
  - The New Wonder World Encyclopedia. Vol. 2. New York: Parents' Magazine's Education Press, 1957., cuid27628 (Box XII.25, Folder 509)
  - ---. Vol. 3 New York: Parents' Magazine's Education Press, 1957., cuid27629 (Box XII.25, Folder 510)
  - ---. Vol. 4 New York: Parents' Magazine's Education Press, 1957., cuid27630 (Box XII.25, Folder 511)
  - ---. Vol. 6 New York: Parents' Magazine's Education Press, 1957., cuid27631 (Box XII.26, Folder 512)
  - ---. Vol. 10 New York: Parents' Magazine's Education Press, 1957., cuid27632 (Box XII.26, Folder 513)
  - New Year! New Talent! Celebrating Emerging Artists of the Eighties. (advertising supplement), cuid27633 (Box XII.26, Folder 514)
  - New York. November 5, 1984., cuid27634 (Box XII.26, Folder 515)
  - ---. June 22, 1987., cuid27635 (Box XII.26, Folder 516)
  - Nietzsche, Friedrich. Beyond Good and Evil. Trans. Walter Kaufmann. New York: Vintage Books/Random House, 1966., cuid27636 (Box XII.26, Folder 535)
  - Nilsson, Lennart. Close to Nature. New York: Pantheon, 1984., cuid27637 (Box XII.26, Folder 536)
  - O'Connor, Flannery. The Complete Stories. New York: Farrar, Straus and Giroux, 1971., cuid27638 (Box XII.26, Folder 537)
  - O'Hara, Frank. Second Avenue. New York: Totem Press/Corinth Books, 1960., cuid27639 (Box XII.26, Folder 538)
  - October. No. 43 Winter 1987., cuid27640 (Box XII.26, Folder 540)
  - Oe, Kenzaburo. Teach Us to Outgrow Our Madness. Trans. John Nathan. New York: Grove Press, 1977., cuid27641 (Box XII.26, Folder 541)
  - The Old Reliable Catalogue. Aug. 1990, cuid27642 (Box XII.26, Folder 542)
  - Organizaciechint. No. 229 Abril/Mayo/Junio. 1983, cuid27643 (Box XII.26, Folder 543)
  - Our Amazing World of Nature. Pleasantville, NY: Reader's Digest Association, 1969. [pages 25, 40, 46, 85, 131, 164-5, 199, 203, 207, 231, 265, 284-5, 302], cuid27644 (Box XII.26, Folder 544)
  - Outweek. No. 63 12 Sept. 1990, cuid27645 (Box XII.26, Folder 546)
  - Outwrite '91. [n. p. ] 1991., cuid27646 (Box XII.26, Folder 547)
  - Owen, Gale R. Rites and Religions of the Anglo-Saxons. New York?: Dorset Press, 1985., cuid27647 (Box XII.26, Folder 548)
  - Pacific Film Archive. Nov. /Dec. 1992, cuid27648 (Box XII.26, Folder 549)
  - Painting and Sculpture Today 1986. Indianapolis: Indianapolis Museum of Art, 1986., cuid27649 (Box XII.26, Folder 550)
  - Palmer, William M. Poisonous Snakes of North Carolina. Raleigh: State Museum of Natural History, 1974., cuid27650 (Box XII.26, Folder 551)
  - Panizza, Oskar. The Council of Love: A Celestial Tragedy in Five Acts. Trans. Oreste F. Pucciani. New York: Viking Press, 1973., cuid27651 (Box XII.26, Folder 552)
  - Paretsky, Sara. Killing Orders. New York: Ballantine, 1985., cuid27652 (Box XII.26, Folder 554)
  - Parkett. No. 21 1989, cuid27653 (Box XII.27, Folder 555)
  - ---. No. 27 1991, cuid27654 (Box XII.27, Folder 556)
  - ---. No. 31 1992, cuid27655 (Box XII.27, Folder 557)
  - Parkhurst, Violet. Painting Sunsets. Tustin, CA: Walter Foster, 1985. (two copies), cuid27656 (Box XII.27, Folder 558)
  - Pasolini, Pier Paolo. The Divine Mimesis. Trans. Thomas Erling Peterson. Berkeley: Double Dance Press, 1980., cuid27657 (Box XII.27, Folder 559)
  - ---. The Ragazzi. Trans. Emile Capouya. Manchester: Carcanet, 1986., cuid27658 (Box XII.27, Folder 560)
  - ---. Roman Nights. Trans. John Shepley. Marlboro, Vt: Marlboro Press, 1986., cuid27659 (Box XII.27, Folder 561)
  - ---. Roman Poems. Trans. Lawrence Ferlinghetti and Francesca Valente. San Francisco: City Lights, 1986., cuid27660 (Box XII.27, Folder 562)
  - ---. The Scent of India. Trans. David Price. London: Olive Press, 1984., cuid27661 (Box XII.27, Folder 563)
  - Patch, Edith M. and Harrison E. Howe. Science at Home. New York: MacMillan, 1937., cuid27662 (Box XII.27, Folder 564)
  - Pato Donald. 21 Apr. 1987, cuid27663 (Box XII.27, Folder 565)
  - Pauline's. New York: Pauline Bernatchez, 1991., cuid27664 (Box XII.27, Folder 566)
  - Pelton, Robert W. and Karen W. Carden. Snake Handlers. Nashville: Thomas Nelson Inc., 1974., cuid27665 (Box XII.27, Folder 567)
  - Perceptions: Black and White. Frances Wolfson Art Gallery. 1986, cuid27666 (Box XII.27, Folder 568)
  - Photography Annual. Photography Magazine. 1954, cuid27667 (Box XII.27, Folder 569)
  - Physique-Art. New York: Roto Color Corp., [n. d. ]., undated; cuid27668 (Box XII.27, Folder 570)
  - Pickwell, Gayle. Weather. Los Angeles: The Junior Literary Guild, 1937., cuid27669 (Box XII.27, Folder 571)
  - Piero Manzoni. New York: Hirschl & Adler Modern, 1990., cuid27670 (Box XII.27, Folder 572)
  - Pittsburgh Center for the Arts. Fall 1983., cuid27671 (Box XII.27, Folder 574)
  - Platt, Rutherford et. al. Secrets of Life: A True-Life Adventure. New York: Simon and Schuster, 1957., cuid27672 (Box XII.27, Folder 575)
  - Playguy. Vol. 3, No. 12, undated; cuid27673 (Box XII.27, Folder 576)
  - Polysexuality. Vol. IV. No. 1 Semiotext(e), 1981., cuid27674 (Box XII.27, Folder 577)
  - Pomerans, Arnold J., trans. A Small Yes and a Big No: The Autobiography of George Grosz. Feltham, UK: Hamlyn Publishing, 1982., cuid27675 (Box XII.27, Folder 578)
  - Pop, Iggy. I Need More. New York: Karz-Cohl Publishing, 1982., cuid27676 (Box XII.27, Folder 579)
  - Popol Vuh. Trans. Ralph Nelson. Boston: Houghton-Mifflin, 1975., cuid27677 (Box XII.27, Folder 580)
  - Portis, Charles. Norwood. New York: Vintage/Random House, 1985., cuid27678 (Box XII.28, Folder 581)
  - Powell, William F. How to Paint Clouds and Skyscapes. Tustin, CA: Foster Art Service, 1987., cuid27679 (Box XII.28, Folder 582)
  - ---. How to Paint Clouds and Skyscapes. Tustin, CA: Foster Art Service, 1989., cuid27680 (Box XII.28, Folder 583)
  - Pox. No. 61 [n. p. ], [n. d. ]., undated; cuid27681 (Box XII.28, Folder 584)
  - Preston-Mafham, Rod and Ken. Spiders of the World. New York: Facts on File Publications, 1984., cuid27682 (Box XII.28, Folder 585)
  - Prignitz-Poda, Helga; ed. Frida Kahlo. Frankfurt: Neue Kritik, 1988., cuid27683 (Box XII.28, Folder 586)
  - Pringle, Laurence. Dinosaurs and Their World. San Diego: Harcourt Brace Jovanovich, 1968. [Note page 35], cuid27684 (Box XII.28, Folder 587)
  - Purdy, James. Cabot Wright Begins. New York: Farrar, Straus & Giroux, 1964., cuid27685 (Box XII.28, Folder 589)
  - PWA Coalition Newsline. Issue #57. Jul. /Aug. 1990, cuid27686 (Box XII.28, Folder 590)
  - ---. Issue #60. Nov. 1990, cuid27687 (Box XII.28, Folder 591)
  - QW. No. 44 6 Sept. 1992, cuid27688 (Box XII.28, Folder 592)
  - Rader, Dotson. I Ain't Marchin' Anymore. New York: Paperback Library, 1964., cuid27689 (Box XII.28, Folder 593)
  - Rand, Ayn. The Fountainhead. New York: Signet, 1971., cuid27690 (Box XII.28, Folder 594)
  - Rechy, John. City of Night. New York: Grove Press, 1963., cuid27691 (Box XII.28, Folder 596)
  - Redrum Magazine: The World of Archie. [n. d. ]; Redrum: The Time of the Assassins [n. d. ]; Redrum: The Charter Arms [n. d. ]., undated; cuid27692 (Box XII.28, Folder 597)
  - Redtape. #4. Fall-Winter 1983-4., 1983-1984; cuid27693 (Box XII.28, Folder 598)
  - Rees, Paul K., Fred W. Sparks and Charles Sparks Rees. Algebra, Trigonometry and Analytic Geometry. New York: McGraw-Hill, 1967., cuid27694 (Box XII.28, Folder 599)
  - Re/Search: William S. Burroughs, Throbbing Gristle, Brion Gysin. San Francisco: Re/Search, 1982., cuid27695 (Box XII.28, Folder 600)
  - Resnick, Robert and David Halliday. Physics. New York: John Wiley, 1966., cuid27696 (Box XII.28, Folder 601)
  - Rey Rosa, Rodrigo. The Beggar's Knife. Trans. Paul Bowles. San Francisco: City Lights, 1985. [page 80 marked], cuid27697 (Box XII.28, Folder 602)
  - Richter, G. M. A. A Handbook of Greek Art. New York: Phaidon Publishers, 1960., cuid27698 (Box XII.29, Folder 603)
  - Rimbaud, Arthur. Illuminations and Other Prose Poems. Trans. Louise Varese. New York: New Directions/James Laughlin, 1957., cuid27699 (Box XII.29, Folder 604)
  - Ringgold, Gene and DeWitt Bodeen. The Films of Cecil B. DeMille. New York: The Citadel Press, 1969., cuid27700 (Box XII.29, Folder 605)
  - Ritter, Bruce. Sometimes God has a Kid's Face. New York: Covenant House, 1988., cuid27701 (Box XII.29, Folder 606)
  - Riverrun. s. l.: 1975., cuid27702 (Box XII.29, Folder 606A.)
  - Robert Frank. Boston: Little, Brown and Co., 1986., cuid27703 (Box XII.29, Folder 607)
  - Rodriguez, Arturo. Mitos en blanco y negro. Madrid: Coleccion arte original, 1979., cuid27704 (Box XII.29, Folder 608)
  - Rolling Stone. Issue 605. 30 May 1991., 1959; cuid27705 (Box XII.29, Folder 609)
  - The Rolling Stone Interviews. New York: St. Martin's Press, 1989., cuid27706 (Box XII.29, Folder 610)
  - Rose, Joel and Catherine Texier; Eds. Between C & D. New York: Penguin, 1988., cuid27707 (Box XII.29, Folder 611)
  - Rosenfeld, Charles, and Robert Cooke. Earthfire: The Eruption of Mount St. Helens. Cambridge, MA: MIT Press, 1982., cuid27708 (Box XII.29, Folder 612)
  - Rosenthal, Mark. Anselm Kiefer. Chicago: Art Institute of Chicago, 1987., cuid27709 (Box XII.29, Folder 613)
  - Sackheim, Eric, ed. The Blues Line: A Collection of Blues Lyrics. New York: Grossman Publishers, 1969., cuid27710 (Box XII.29, Folder 614)
  - Sagan, Carl, and Ann Druyan. Comet. New York: Random House, 1985., cuid27711 (Box XII.29, Folder 615)
  - Saint, Assoto; ed. The Road Before Us. New York: Galiens Press, 1991., cuid27712 (Box XII.29, Folder 616)
  - Saint sstien dans l'histoire de l'art depuis le xv sie. Paris: Jacques Damase Editeur, 1979., cuid27713 (Box XII.29, Folder 617)
  - Samuels, Peggy and Harold. Contemporary Western Artists. New York: Bonanza Books, 1982., cuid27714 (Box XII.30, Folder 618)
  - San Francisco Review of Books. Vol. 16, No. 1 Summer 1991., cuid27715 (Box XII.30, Folder 619)
  - Scavullo, Francesco. Men. New York: Random House, 1977., cuid27716 (Box XII.30, Folder 620)
  - Schidor, Dieter, and Michael McLernon, eds. Rainer Werner Fassbinder: Querelle, the Film Book. Munchen: Schirmer/Mosel Verlag, 1982., cuid27717 (Box XII.30, Folder 621)
  - Scholder, Amy and Ira Silverberg; Eds. High Risk. New York: Penguin, 1991., cuid27718 (Box XII.30, Folder 622)
  - Schulz, Bruno. Sanatorium under the Sign of the Hourglass. Trans. Celina Wieniewska. New York: Penguin, 1979., cuid27719 (Box XII.30, Folder 623)
  - ---. The Street of Crocodiles. New York: Penguin, 1963., cuid27720 (Box XII.30, Folder 624)
  - Schwab, Gustav. Gods and Heroes: Myths and Epics of Ancient Greece. New York: Pantheon, 1974., cuid27721 (Box XII.30, Folder 625)
  - Schwartz, Eugene M. The Sound of One Mind Thinking. San Francisco: Strawberry Hill Press, 1981., cuid27722 (Box XII.30, Folder 626)
  - Science. 3 Feb. 1988, cuid27723 (Box XII.30, Folder 627)
  - Sculpture Show: Neue Skulpturen aus der East Village. Koln: Anna Friebe Galerie, 1984?, cuid27724 (Box XII.30, Folder 628)
  - Segaller, Stephen and Merrill Berger. The Wisdom of the Dream: The World of C. G. Jung. Boston: Shambhala, 1989., cuid27725 (Box XII.30, Folder 629)
  - Seisser, Jean. Herve DiRosa. Paris?: Le Dernier Terrain Vague, 1983., cuid27726 (Box XII.30, Folder 630)
  - Serpent's Tail Catalogue. April-Dec. 1992, cuid27727 (Box XII.30, Folder 631)
  - 750 Warme Berliner. Berlin: Verlag rosa Berliner, 1987., cuid27728 (Box XII.30, Folder 632)
  - Seymour, Jacqueline. La Naturaleza: Los Hongos. Trans. Ramon Menal Armisen. Barcelona: Ediciones Castell, [n. d. ]., undated; cuid27729 (Box XII.30, Folder 633)
  - ---. La Naturaleza: El Mundo Natural. Barcelona: Ediciones Castell, [n. d. ]., undated; cuid27730 (Box XII.30, Folder 634)
  - Shepard, Sam. Motel Chronicles & Hawk Moon. London: Faber & Faber, 1985., cuid27731 (Box XII.30, Folder 635)
  - Sherman, Charles L. Nature's Wonders. Garden City, NY: Hanover House, 1956., cuid27732 (Box XII.30, Folder 636)
  - Shiny. No. 6 Spring/Summer 1991., cuid27733 (Box XII.30, Folder 637)
  - Shomer, Louis. Police Jiu-Jitsu. New York: Book-A-Mag Co., 1940., cuid27734 (Box XII.30, Folder 638)
  - Siddha Path. [n. p. ], [n. d. ]., undated; cuid27735 (Box XII.31, Folder 639)
  - Sidenbladh, Erik. Les Bs de l'eau. Trans. Christian Bounay. Paris: Editions Robert Laffont, 1982., cuid27736 (Box XII.31, Folder 640)
  - Siegle, Robert. Suburban Ambush. Baltimore: Johns Hopkins Press, 1989., cuid27737 (Box XII.31, Folder 641)
  - Sigmar Polke. Koln: Josef-Haubrich-Kunsthalle, 1984., cuid27738 (Box XII.31, Folder 642)
  - Sloane, R. K. A Real Gein ~Zine. Albuquerque, NM: R. K. Sloane, 1985. / Smithsonian Scientific Series. Old and New Plant Lore. Vol. 11 U. S.: Smithsonian Institution Series Inc., 1931., cuid27739 (Box XII.31, Folder 644)
  - Smithsonian. Dec. 1975 [Note: AHobo article@], cuid27740 (Box XII.31, Folder 645)
  - The Snakes of New Jersey. Reprinted from New Jersey Outdoors. [n. p. ] [n. d. ]., undated; cuid27741 (Box XII.31, Folder 646)
  - Social Studies: Truth, Justice and the Afro-American Way. Normal: University Galleries, 1989., cuid27742 (Box XII.31, Folder 647)
  - Space Images. New York: Lustrum Press, 1982., cuid27743 (Box XII.31, Folder 648)
  - Spiegelman, Art. Maus II. New York: Pantheon Books, 1991., cuid27744 (Box XII.31, Folder 649)
  - Spin. June 1991., cuid27745 (Box XII.31, Folder 650)
  - Splendeurs et Miss du Corps. Paris: Paris Audiovisuel, 1988., cuid27746 (Box XII.31, Folder 651)
  - Sproule, Anna. Wild Animals. London: Octopus Books Ltd., 1979., cuid27747 (Box XII.31, Folder 652)
  - Stanek, V. J. Introducing Monkeys. Trans. George Theiner. London: Spring Books, [n. d. ]. [source material], undated; cuid27748 (Box XII.31, Folder 654)
  - ---. The Pictorial Encyclopedia of Insects. London: Paul Hamlyn, 1969., cuid27749 (Box XII.31, Folder 655)
  - Stephens, John L. Incidents of Travel in Yucatan. Vol. 1 &2. Mexico City: Panorama Editorial, 1988., cuid27750 (Box XII.31, Folder 659)
  - Stern [German-language magazine]. January 1984., cuid27751 (Box XII.31, Folder 660)
  - Stern, Jane. Trucker. New York: McGraw-HIll, 1975., cuid27752 (Box XII.31, Folder 661)
  - Stewart, James B. Den of Thieves. New York: Touchstone, 1992., cuid27753 (Box XII.31, Folder 662)
  - Stirling, Matthew W. Indians of the Americas. Washington, D. C.: The National Geographic Society, 1955., cuid27754 (Box XII.32, Folder 663)
  - Sturgis, J. E. Evangelistic Edition of Wonder Hymns of Faith. Cincinnati: The Standard Publishing Co., [n. d. ]., undated; cuid27755 (Box XII.32, Folder 664)
  - Surgence. Paris: Aubin Imprimeur, 1991., cuid27756 (Box XII.32, Folder 665)
  - Sutton, Ann and Myron Sutton. Eastern Forests. New York: Alfred A. Knopf, 1987., cuid27757 (Box XII.32, Folder 666)
  - Swain, Ralph B. The Insect Guide. Garden City, NY: Doubleday, 1948., cuid27758 (Box XII.32, Folder 667)
  - Swami Dayananda and Janaki Vunderink; eds. Hatha Yoga. South Fallsburg, NY: SYDA Foundation, 1981., cuid27759 (Box XII.32, Folder 668)
  - Sweeney, James B. A Pictorial History of Sea Monsters. New York: Bonanza Books, 1972., cuid27760 (Box XII.32, Folder 669)
  - Szarkowski, John; Ed. From the Picture Press. New York: MOMA Press, 1973., cuid27761 (Box XII.32, Folder 670)
  - ---. Mirrors and Windows. New York: The Museum of Modern Art, 1978., cuid27762 (Box XII.32, Folder 671)
  - Takahashi, Mutsuo. Poems of a Penisist. Trans. Hiroaki Sato. Chicago: Chicago Review Press, 1975., cuid27763 (Box XII.32, Folder 672)
  - Tales from the Crypt. No. 2 Sept 1990., cuid27764 (Box XII.32, Folder 673)
  - Tanaka, Seiichi. The Avant-Gardes in New York. Japan: 1986., cuid27765 (Box XII.32, Folder 674)
  - Taxidermy for the Amateur. New York: G. Schoepfer, [n. d. ]., undated; cuid27766 (Box XII.32, Folder 675)
  - Tedlock, Dennis, ed. Popol Vuh: The Mayan Book of the Dawn of Life. New York: Touchstone/Simon & Schuster, 1985., cuid27767 (Box XII.32, Folder 676)
  - Terra-Cotta Warriors and Horses at the Tomb of Qin Shi Huang. [n. p. ]: [n. d. ]., undated; cuid27768 (Box XII.32, Folder 677)
  - Thinking of You. [n. p. ]: April House, 1976., cuid27769 (Box XII.32, Folder 678)
  - Third Text. Summer 1990., cuid27770 (Box XII.32, Folder 679)
  - 36 Works, 18 Artists, 6 Galleries, 1 Alma Mater. Bronxville, NY: Sarah Lawrence College Gallery, 1982., cuid27771 (Box XII.32, Folder 680)
  - Tillman, Lynne. Living With Contradictions. New York: Top Stories, 1982., cuid27772 (Box XII.32, Folder 681)
  - Tillman, Lynne. Madame Realism. New York: The Print Center, 1984., cuid27773 (Box XII.32, Folder 682)